

□ adam.drag@yahoo.com

206 619 0677

Phoenix, AZ

in linkedin.com/in/adamdrag

DEV PORTFOLIO

adamdrag.com

DEV SKILLS

Agile Scrum

HTML5, CSS3

Bootstrap, Semantic

Sass, React Bootstrap

JavaScript, jQuery

React, Redux

Node, Express

WordPress, PHP

MySQL

MongoDB, Firebase

Mocha, Jest

Gulp, Webpack

Git, GitHub, GitLab

Jira/Confluence

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

SOFT SKILLS

Team leadership

Ops management

Process improvement

Decision-making

Problem solving

Analytics and reporting

ADAM DRAG

Tech-savvy, self-starter with expertise and academic training in writing well-designed, testable and efficient code. Experienced in an array of scripting languages and multimedia Web tools. Able to handle dynamic workloads and optimize projects to exceed business goals. Proven team leader and team player with a positive, can-do attitude. Driven to continuously learn and improve.

EDUCATION

Advanced Developer Training Program, IntraEdge - 2019

Full-stack developer, Coding Boot Camp, University of Arizona - 2019

Certificate of Information Technology, Kent Institute of Business & Technology - 2004

Business Diploma, Marketing, Australian Pacific College – 2007

Bachelor's Degree, Behavioral Psychology, Warsaw School of Pedagogy – 2002

WORK EXPERIENCE

IntraEdge Phoenix, AZ

Feb 2019 to current

Entry-Level Programmer

Completed Dev Training Program. Learning advanced programming, coding techniques and testing with exercises and group projects in agile environment.

Cruise - General Motors Phoenix, AZ

Sept 2016 to Jan 2019

Intranet Developer

Designed, developed and maintained a custom company Intranet site for secure intradepartment communications, new policy acknowledgement, training tracking, Wiki, shift scheduling, project status and reporting in WordPress.

Team Lead

Led and trained Automated Vehicle Trainers team of 24 in testing automated vehicles. Managed garage operations, vehicle fleets and investigated/resolved AV system errors. Developed team management processes, in-vehicle training materials and procedures, and optimized AVT performance and communications.

Drive Classification Technician

Investigate and determine outcomes of automated vehicle system dis-engagements. Provide detailed analysis and classification for engineering resolution.

FALCK Northwest Seattle, WA

Sep 2015 – Aug 2016

Emergency Medical Technician

Provided ambulance and emergency services to public, including hospitals, clinics and extended-care facilities. Provided emergency services and patient support with perfect service call and ambulance driving record - 100% successful call completion.

International Australia, England, Poland

2000 - 2015

Sales Manager: Managed daily operations in book wholesale. Developed and implemented operating procedures, managed budget, supervised staff, resolved client issues and ensured profitability.

Shop Manager: Managed daily operations of coffee shop. Maintained inventory, recruited and supervised staff including shift scheduling, supplier liaisons, managed budget, enforced hygiene and safety regulations and resolved customers issues.